Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
War poster collection
1913-1986
1914-1918
MS 671
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
14.83
(237 folio folders and three boxes)
The collection consists of posters published in nations involved in World War I, 1914-1918, the Spanish Civil War, and World War II, 1939-1945. Great Britain, the United States, France, Germany, Italy, Russia, Canada, Australia, Ireland and other nations are represented through posters depicting such diverse topics as recruitment, enlistment, conservation, war loans, civilian service, home relief, foreign relief and propaganda messages. Posters issued by government agencies, social organizations, and private concerns are included.
Allen, Lafon
Atkins, Paul M. (Paul Moody), 1892-
Brett, Simon, 1945-
Darrot, Paul Jean Gaston, 1892-1958
House, Edward Mandell, 1858-1938
Mullally, William
Vail, George
Whittelsey, Charles Barney, 1869-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Lafon Allen, 1937, and several others; transferred from the Medical Historical Library, 1990, and the Librarian's Office, 1995; Library purchase, 2004; transferred from the Kaplanoff Librarian for American History, 2016.
Conditions Governing Access
Accession 2007-M-065 is restricted pending conservation treatment.
Existence and Location of Copies
Approximately 200 posters from series I and II are available in digital form through Manuscripts and Archives Digital Image Database (MADID).
William Mullally Collection available on microfilm (2 reels, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, at cost. Order no. HM157.
Biographical / Historical
The War Poster Collection is a composite of several individual donations and library purchases, accumulated from the 1920s through the 1980s, and 2004. Individual donations, such as that of Lafon Allen, are identified within the War Poster Collection, as single collections themselves.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of posters disseminated by and published in nations involved in World War I, 1914-1918, the Spanish Civil War, and World War II, 1939-1945. Great Britain, the United States, France, Germany, Italy, Russia, Canada, Australia, Ireland and other nations are represented through posters depicting such diverse topics as recruitment, enlistment, conservation, war loans, civilian service, home relief, foreign relief and propaganda messages. Posters issued by government agencies, social organizations, and private concerns are included.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in three series: I. World War I, 1914- 1918, II. Spanish Civil War, 1936-1939, III World War II, 1939-1945, and three additions.
Other Finding Aids
For an index of artists represented in this collection, please consult the Index of Artists.
For an index of subject terms used to describe this collection, please consult the Subject Terms Index.
Posters, Australian; Posters, Austrian; Posters, Belgian; Posters, Canadian; Posters, Chinese; Posters, Czech; Posters, Dutch; Posters, East Indian; Posters, French; Posters, German; Posters, Greek; Posters, Hungarian; Posters, Irish; Posters, Italian; Posters, Polish; Posters, Russian; Posters, Swiss; Posters, Turkish; Proclamations -- Great Britain; Propaganda, American; Propaganda, British; Propaganda, French; Propaganda, German; United States -- Proclamations; World War, 1914-1918 -- Economic aspects -- France; World War, 1914-1918 -- Economic aspects -- Germany; World War, 1914-1918 -- Economic aspects -- Great Britain; World War, 1914-1918 -- Economic aspects -- United States; World War, 1914-1918 -- Equipment and supplies -- France; World War, 1914-1918 -- Equipment and supplies -- Germany; World War, 1914-1918 -- Equipment and supplies -- Great Britain; World War, 1914-1918 -- Equipment and supplies -- United States; World War, 1914-1918 -- Finance -- France; World War, 1914-1918 -- Finance -- Germany; World War, 1914-1918 -- Finance -- Great Britain; World War, 1914-1918 -- Finance -- United States; World War, 1914-1918 -- Food supply -- France; World War, 1914-1918 -- Food supply -- Germany; World War, 1914-1918 -- Food supply -- Great Britain; World War, 1914-1918 -- Food supply -- United States; World War, 1914-1918 -- Propaganda; World War, 1914-1918 -- War work -- Young Men's Christian Associations; World War, 1914-1918 -- War work; World War, 1914-1918 -- Women; World War, 1939-1945 -- Propaganda; France -- Proclamations; Germany -- History -- Revolution, 1918 -- Posters; Germany -- Proclamations; Spain -- History -- Civil War, 1936-1939; Posters; Proclamations; France. Armée -- Recruiting, enlistment, etc -- World War, 1914-1918; Germany. Heer -- Recruiting, enlistment, etc.; Great Britain. Army -- Recruiting, enlistment, etc.; Great Britain. National Savings Committee; Great Britain. Parliamentary War Savings Committee; United States. Army -- Recruiting, enlistment, etc -- World War, 1914-1919; United States. Marine Corps; United States. Navy ( Recruiting, enlistment, etc.); American Committee for Relief in the Near East; American Library Association; American National Red Cross; Business Men's Week; Church Army (Church of England); Croce rossa italiana; National Catholic War Council (Wash. D.C.); National Jewish Welfare Board; Queen Mary's Army Recruiting Corps; Salvation Army -- Great Britain; Salvation Army -- United States; Scottish War Savings Committee; U. S. Fuel Administration; U. S. Shipping Board; U. S. War Exposition; U. S. War Garden Commission
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, World War I, 1914-1918, contains approximately 3,000 posters produced during this war.
  The information provided for each poster is as follows. 1. An item number comprised of a one-letter designation representing the individual collection (which forms part of the larger poster collection) in which the item is arranged: A - Lafon Allen Collection, W - Charles B. Whittelsey Collection, Y - Yale Library Collection; a two- letter designation for the country under which the poster is arranged within the individual collection: AU (Austria), BE (Belgium), CA (Canada), CZ (Czechoslovakia), FR (France), GB (Great Britain), GE (Germany), GR (Greece), HO (Holland), HU (Hungary), IN (India), IT (Italy), MX (Mexico), PO (Poland), RU (Soviet Union), SW (Switzerland), US (United States); and a four-character numeral designation for a poster within its collection/country code. Example: ABE001. 2. Title. The title appearing on the poster. Use of an ellipsis ["…"] signifies that the title continues beyond what is provided here. 3. Date. The year, month, and day (when known) for publication of the poster. 4. Size. The physical dimensions of the poster, in inches with fractional measurements rounded off to the higher number. 5. Language. The language of the poster's text. 6. Artist. The name of the artist who created the poster. 7. Place of publication. The country in which (or for which) the poster was produced. This may differ from the "Country Code" as in the case of Great Britain posters) which include items created for and in Australia, Canada, and Ireland. 8. Notes. Comments about the item including number of pieces or description of an untitled image.
  - Lafon Allen Collection
    - Austria
      - Zeichnet 6te, Kriegsanleihe, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AAU0001; 25x38 inches (Box 1)
        Artist: Stisborsky, Willly. Place of Publication: Austria.
      - Ausstellung Handgefertigter Arbeiten Osterreich, 1917 March; AAU0002; 24x37 inches (Box 1)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Austria.
      - Zeichnet die Dechste Kriegsanleihe, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AAU0003; 21x30 inches (Box 1)
        Artist: Lenz, M.. Place of Publication: Austria.
      - Lesset die Flagge, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AAU0004; 24x38 inches (Box 1)
      - Zeichnet die Sechste Kriegsanleihe, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AAU0005; 35x53 inches (Box 1)
        Artist: A.S.. Place of Publication: Austria.
      - Zlichnet Funste Osterreichische Kriegsanleihe, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AAU0006; 35x47 inches (Box 1)
      - Cabaret. Am 3 und 4 Marx. Marcs s an es 4 en., 1917; AAU0007; 20x27 inches (Box 1)
        Artist: Bato. Place of Publication: Austria.
    - Belgium
      - Emprunt de la Restauration Nationale, 1919; ABE0001; 35x26 inches (Box 2)
        Artist: Paulus, F.. Place of Publication: Belgium.
      - Institution Royale de Messines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ABE0002; 32x47 inches (Box 2)
        Artist: Fouqueray, D. Charles. Place of Publication: Belgium.
    - Czechoslovakia
      - Czechoslovak! Join Our Free Colors! School of Printing and Graphic Art of Wentworth Institute, Boston., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ACZ0001; 25x36 inches (Box 3)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Czechoslovakia.
      - Kdoiste Bozibojovnici, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ACZ0002; 25x36 inches (Box 3)
      - Hrr Navraha! Za Demokracii!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ACZ0003; 25x36 inches (Box 3)
      - Manifest K Ceskoslovenskemu lidu V Americe!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ACZ0004; 25x36 inches (Box 3)
      - Uz Slovenskovstava, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ACZ0005; 25x36 inches (Box 3)
      - Boh do Krivdy Hromon, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; ACZ0006; 25x36 inches (Box 3)
    - France
      - Republique Francaise - Liberte, Egalite, Fraternite, 1914 August 4; AFR0001; 25x36 inches (Box 4)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: France.
      - Republique Francaise - Liberte, Egalite, Fraternite, 1914 August 4; AFR0002; 25x36 inches (Box 4)
      - A la Nation Francaise., 1914 July; AFR0003; 25x36 inches (Box 4)
      - Armee de Terre et Armee de Mer - Odre de Mobilisation Generale, 1914 August 2; AFR0004; 25x36 inches (Box 4)
      - Gouvernement Militaire de Paris - Armee de Paris, 1914 September 3; AFR0005; 20x25 inches (Box 4)
      - Republique Francaise. Appel du Calme. Avis Tres Important, 1914 September 2; AFR0006; 20x26 inches (Box 4)
      - Franzoischen Republik - Burgenmeisterei der Stadt Epernay, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0007; 20x27 inches (Box 4)
      - Ville d'Amiens, 1914 September 2; AFR0008; 2x18 inches (Box 4)
      - Le Maire d'Amiens Felicite ses Concitoyens, 1914 September 1; AFR0009; 22x18 inches (Box 4)
      - Prefecture de Loir-and-Cher. Mesures de Police concernant, 1914 December 3; AFR0010; 26x36 inches (Box 4)
      - INSTRUCTIONS - En cas d' atterrissage d'Aeroplanes sur le, 1916 April 22; AFR0011; 22x30 inches (Box 4)
      - Abri. Profondeur de 5 a 7 Metres., 1917; AFR0012; 22x17 inches (Box 4)
      - Cette Station n'est pas classee comme Abri., 1917; AFR0013; 19x13 inches (Box 4)
      - Abri. Descendez avec Calme Degagez les Acces., 1917; AFR0014; 19x13 inches (Box 4)
      - Defense de Stationner dans la Salle de Distribution des Billets, 1917; AFR0015; 19x13 inches (Box 4)
      - Liste des Stations Classees comme Abris en cas d'Alerte, 1918 February; AFR0016; 11x18 inches (Box 4)
      - Mesures Prescrites en cas d'Incursion d'aeronefs ennemis, 1918 February 4; AFR0017; 18x22 inches (Box 5)
      - Commemoration en France de l'Independence des Etats Unis, 1918 June 28; AFR0018; 22x30 inches (Box 5)
      - Recrutement de l'Armee. Classe 1920. Conseil de Revision, 1918 August 22; AFR0019; 20x26 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise. Conseil Municipal de Paris, 1918 November; AFR0020; 18x25 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise. Chambre de Deputes, 1918 December 11; AFR0021; 36x44 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise, 1918 December 17; AFR0022; 22x35 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise. Chambre de Deputes, 1919 January 16; AFR0023; 36x45 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise, 1919 January 15; AFR0024; 22x34 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise, 1918 November 19; AFR0025; 29x47 inches (Box 5)
      - Franzosische Republik - Der Kommissar der Republik an die Franzosen., 1918 November 19; AFR0026; 29x47 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise. La Commissaire de la Republique, 1918; AFR0027; 29x47 inches (Box 5)
      - Franzosische Republik-Der Kommissar der Republik, 1918 November 19; AFR0028; 29x47 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise; Prefecture de la Seine. Avis, 1917 December 4; AFR0029; 20x26 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise; Declaration du Gouvernement, 1917 November 20; AFR0030; 25x38 inches (Box 5)
      - Republique Francaise, Chambre des Deputes, 1918 January 10; AFR0031; 36x44 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Prefecture de Police. Conseils a la, 1918 February 25; AFR0032; 18x35 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Union des Societes d'Education Physique, 1916; AFR0033; 33x25 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise. A la France de Demain! A la Jeunesse, 1918 July; AFR0034; 25x32 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise. Department de Seine-et-Oise, 1918 July; AFR0035; 17x22 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise. Chambre des Deputes, 1918 September 5; AFR0036; 35x44 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise, 1918 September 17; AFR0037; 25x39 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise. Chambre de Deputes, 1918 November 7; AFR0038; 34x45 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Ville de Joinville-le-Pont, 1918 July 24; AFR0039; 17x25 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise...Hommage aux Allies Victorieux, 1918 November 7; AFR0040; 25x39 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Chambre de Deputes, 1918 November 11; AFR0041; 36x44 inches (Box 6)
      - Discourse…, 1918 November 17; AFR0042; 29x45 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Gloire a la Belgique, 1915 December 21; AFR0043; 25x33 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Chambre de Deputes, 1918 October 18; AFR0044; 35x44 inches (Box 6)
      - Republique Francaise; Chambre de Deputes, 1918 October 22; AFR0045; 36x44 inches (Box 6)
      - Mission Militaire Francaise Attache a l'Armee Britannique, 1918 September 1; AFR0046; 09x13 inches (Box 7)
      - Republique Francaise. Ministre de la Guerre. Instructions, 1917; AFR0047; 14x18 inches (Box 7)
      - ACCORD entre le Gouvernement de la Republique Francaise, 1918; AFR0048; 19x25 inches (Box 7)
      - Ville de Dunkerque Retour de Monsieur President de la Republique, 1914; AFR0049; 26x38 inches (Box 7)
      - DUNKERQUOIS, Les Bombardements que nous venons de subir ont fait, 1915 May 2; AFR0050; 26x20 inches (Box 7)
      - Maire de Bordeaux. Recruitement de l'Armee, 1918; AFR0051; 25x40 inches (Box 7)
      - Direction des Etapes de l'Ouest., 1918 July 20; AFR0052; 11x18 inches (Box 7)
      - Ville de Versailles. Signal d'Alerte Clairons, 1918 March 16; AFR0053; 11x17 inches (Box 7)
      - Ville de Versailles. Alertes, 1918 March 14; AFR0054; 18x11 inches (Box 7)
      - Cour de Justice, Extrait des Minutes de Greffe de la Cour, 1918 August 6; AFR0055; 19x26 inches (Box 7)
      - Ministere de l'Interieur. Changement de l'Heure, 1916 June; AFR0056; 22x30 inches (Box 7)
      - A Toute la Jeunesse Scolaire, 1917; AFR0057; 24x33 inches (Box 7)
      - Commemoration. La Protestation des Deputes d'Alsace, 1916 June; AFR0058; 20x26 inches (Box 7)
      - Republique Francaise. Ville de Versailles. Preliminaires, 1919 April 27; AFR0059; 26x33 inches (Box 7)
      - Republique Francaise. Ville de Versailles Femeture des Trianon, 1919 April 28; AFR0060; 18x11 inches (Box 7)
      - Republique Francaise Ministere de l'Interieure, 1918 July; AFR0061; 23x30 inches (Box 7)
      - Aux Armees Francaises. Proclamation du Roy George V. Soldats, 1917 July 12; AFR0062; 24x33 inches (Box 7)
      - Republique Francaise. Ordre du Jour du General Petain, 1917 July 3; AFR0063; 24x33 inches (Box 7)
      - Ville de Dunkerque. Pour Nos Rapatries, 1918 December 18; AFR0064; 19x25 inches (Box 7)
      - 2me. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale., 1916; AFR0065; 30x46 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Robaudi. Place of Publication: France.
      - Deuxieme Emprunt de la Defense Nationale., 1916; AFR0066; 25x34 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Lechaudel. Place of Publication: France.
      - Deuxieme Emprunt de la Defense Nationale., 1916; AFR0067; 25x34 inches (Box 8)
      - Francais Souscrivez au Deuxieme Emprunt., 1916; AFR0068; 30x46 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Naudin, Bernard. Place of Publication: France.
      - 2me Emprunt de la Defense Nationale., 1916; AFR0069; 24x30 inches (Box 8)
      - On les Aura., 1916; AFR0070; 32x46 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Faivre, Jules Abel. Place of Publication: France.
      - 2e Emprunt 5% de la Defense Nationale., 1916; AFR0071; 13x18 inches (Box 8)
        Scope and Contents note
      - 2eme Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1916; AFR0072; 11x15 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Hansi. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour le Drapeau! Pour la Victoire!, 1917; AFR0073; 31x47 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Scott, Georges. Place of Publication: France.
      - Souscrivez pour Hater la Paix par la Victoire., 1917; AFR0074; 44x31 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Besnard, Paul Albert. Place of Publication: France.
      - 2eme. Emprunt Nationale. Rente 4%, 1917; AFR0075; 31x47 inches (Box 8)
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1917; AFR0076; 28x43 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Kivitsky. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour la Liberte du Monde, 1917; AFR0077; 30x47 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Sem.; Goursat, Georges. Place of Publication: France.
      - Debout dans la tranchee que l'aurore eclaire, le soldat reve, 1917; AFR0078; 31x45 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Droit, Lieutenant Jean. Place of Publication: France.
      - Compagnie Algerienne...3e Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1917; AFR0079; 31x46 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Jonas, Lucien-Hector. Place of Publication: France.
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1917; AFR0080; 31x45 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Leroux, Auguste. Place of Publication: France.
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1917; AFR0081; 47x32 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: LeLong, A.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Souscrivez tous au 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1917; AFR0082; 11x14 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Hansi.; Waltz, Jean Jacques. Place of Publication: France.
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale., 1917 December; AFR0083; 17x25 inches (Box 8)
      - Compagnie des Agents de Change de Paris, 3eme. Emprunt, 1917; AFR0084; 31x48 inches (Box 8)
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale., 1917; AFR0085; 22x31 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Knight, Ridgway. Place of Publication: France.
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale Credit Lyonnais, 1917; AFR0086; 16x24 inches (Box 8)
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale Credit Lyonnais, 1917; AFR0087; 31x47 inches (Box 8)
      - Passant! Fais tout ton devoir, 1917; AFR0088; 37x25 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Carlu, Jacques. Place of Publication: France.
      - 3e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale. La Souscription, 1917; AFR0089; 32x47 inches (Box 8)
        Artist: Tel. Place of Publication: France.
      - Emprunt de la Deliberation: On les a., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0090; 32x47 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: Bouisset, E.M.F.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Un Dernier Effort et On l'aura., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0091; 31x47 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: Courboin, Eug. Place of Publication: France.
      - (Untitled), Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0092; 29x36 inches (Box 9)
      - Credit Commercial de France, 1918; AFR0093; 32x46 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: Jonas, Lucien - Hector. Place of Publication: France.
      - Credit Commercial de France, 1918; AFR0094; 32x46 inches (Box 9)
      - Pour que la France soit Victorieuse!, 1918; AFR0095; 32x44 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: Scott, George.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour en finir une bonne fois!, 1918; AFR0096; 24x32 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: Aurisse. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour nous rendre entiere la Douce Terre de France, 1918; AFR0097; 47x32 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: Chavannaz, B.. Place of Publication: France.
      - EMPRUNT National 1918 - Souscrivez pour la Victoire qui vient!, AFR0098; 45x31 inches (Box 9)
      - Pour le Retour Souscrivez, 1918; AFR0099; 46x32 inches (Box 9)
        Artist: P.,R.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Emprunt de la Defense Nationale - On Souscrit a la Banque Adam, 1918; AFR0100; 24x32 inches (Box 9)
      - Pour Achever la Croisade du Droit Souscrivez, 1918; AFR0101; 32x44 inches (Box 10)
        Artist: Chavanna, B.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Comptoir National d'Escompte de Paris, 1918; AFR0102; 32x47 inches (Box 10)
      - Pour le Retour du Soldat Vainqueur Souscrivez au credit du Nord., 1918; AFR0103; 46x32 inches (Box 10)
      - Banque Industrielle de Chine; 4e. Emprunt National., 1918; AFR0104; 32x47 inches (Box 10)
        Artist: Baste. Place of Publication: France.
      - 4e. Emprunt National, 1918; AFR0105; 32x47 inches (Box 10)
        Artist: Droit, Jean. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour le supreme Effort, 1918; AFR0106; 32x47 inches (Box 10)
        Artist: Falter, M.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Emprunt Francais 4% 1918, AFR0107; 24x32 inches (Box 10)
      - 4e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1918; AFR0108; 31x47 inches (Box 10)
      - Compagnie Algerienne, 1918; AFR0109; 32x47 inches (Box 10)
        Artist: Romberg, M.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Francais pour la liberation du Territoire Souscrivez., 1918; AFR0110; 47x33 inches (Box 10)
      - 1918 Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, AFR0111; 28x40 inches (Box 11)
      - Emprunt de la Liberation 1918, AFR0112; 32x44 inches (Box 11)
      - Pour le Dernier Quart d'Heure, 1918; AFR0113; 47x32 inches (Box 11)
        Artist: Sem.; Goursat, Georges.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Film de l'Emprunt 1918. La Conversation du Pere Grandet., AFR0114; 31x47 inches (Box 11)
      - Banque de l'Union Parisienne, 1918; AFR0115; 32x48 inches (Box 11)
        Artist: Willette, Adolphe Leon. Place of Publication: France.
      - L'Emprunt de la Liberation., 1918; AFR0116; 44x32 inches (Box 11)
      - Societe Marseillaise de Credit, 1918; AFR0117; 31x47 inches (Box 11)
      - Compagnie des Notaires, 1918; AFR0118; 31x44 inches (Box 11)
      - 4e. Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, 1918; AFR0119; 23x32 inches (Box 11)
      - Italiens, Souscrivez au 4eme. Emprunt, 1918; AFR0120; 32x44 inches (Box 11)
      - Banque Francaise, 1918; AFR0121; 32x47 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Malherbe, William. Place of Publication: France.
      - Emprunt de la Liberation, 1918; AFR0122; 31x45 inches (Box 12)
      - Credit Lyonnais. Souscrivez au 43. Emprunt National., 1918; AFR0123; 24x32 inches (Box 12)
      - Emprunt de la Liberation. On Souscrit a la Banque d'Alsace, 1918; AFR0124; 24x31 inches (Box 12)
      - Souscrivez a l'Emprunt a la Societe Centrale des Banques, 1918; AFR0125; 32x48 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Courboin, Eugene. Place of Publication: France.
      - Un Dernier Effort et on l'Aura, 1918; AFR0126; 30x46 inches (Box 12)
      - Souscrivez au Iveme. Emprunt et le Drapeau Tricolore, 1918; AFR0127; 24x31 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Hansi.; Waltz, Jean Jacques.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Appel du Ministre de l'Instruction Publique et des Beaux-Arts, 1918 October; AFR0128; 15x25 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Prouve, V.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Les Chansons de Jacquot et de Marie Annette, 1918; AFR0129; 11x15 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Metivet, Lucien. Place of Publication: France.
      - Ceux qui Perdent de l'Argent par Leur Faute, 1918; AFR0130; 11x15 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Vincent, Rene. Place of Publication: France.
      - Petits Sous, Que Deviendrez-Vous?, 1918; AFR0131; 11x15 inches (Box 12)
        Artist: Bougle. Place of Publication: France.
      - Notre Victoire Financiere, 1918 October; AFR0132; 19x23 inches (Box 12)